{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Question 1",
      "details": "Which number is 58,000,000 when rounded to the nearest million?",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "57,422,000",
        "choice2": "57,449,000",
        "choice3": "57,651,000",
        "choice4": "57,499,000"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 2",
      "details": "Round number 79,000 to the nearest ten thousand",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "79,000",
        "choice2": "80,000",
        "choice3": "89,000",
        "choice4": "90,000"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 3",
      "details": "Rounding number 3,456,786 to the nearest hundred thousand.",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "3,456,786",
        "choice2": "3,450,000",
        "choice3": "3,400,000",
        "choice4": "3,500,000"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 4,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 4",
      "details": "Which number is 58,000,000 when rounded to the nearest million?",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "57,422,000",
        "choice2": "57,449,000",
        "choice3": "57,651,000",
        "choice4": "57,499,000"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 5",
      "details": "Which number is 200 when rounded to the nearest hundred?",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "120",
        "choice2": "140",
        "choice3": "240",
        "choice4": "250"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 6",
      "details": "Which number is 1,000 when rounded to the nearest thousand?",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "1,500",
        "choice2": "1,499",
        "choice3": "2,400",
        "choice4": "1,600"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 7",
      "details": "Which number is 1,850 when rounded to the nearest ten?",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "1,815",
        "choice2": "1,851",
        "choice3": "1,844",
        "choice4": "1,855"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 8",
      "details": "Which number is 700 when rounded to the nearest hundred?",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "520",
        "choice2": "540",
        "choice3": "640",
        "choice4": "650"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 4,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 9",
      "details": "Which number is 7,600,000 when rounded to the nearest hundred thousand?",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "7,622,000",
        "choice2": "7,649,000",
        "choice3": "7,651,000",
        "choice4": "7,649,000"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 10",
      "details": "How many hundreds in 100,000?",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "1 hundred",
        "choice2": "10 hundreds",
        "choice3": "100 hundreds",
        "choice4": "1000 hundreds"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 4,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 11",
      "details": "What is the smallest whole number that is 5,000 when rounded to the nearest thousand",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "4,500",
        "choice2": "4,499",
        "choice3": "4,450",
        "choice4": "4,599"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 12",
      "details": "What is the greatest whole number that is 5,000 when rounded to the nearest thousand",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "5,199",
        "choice2": "5,299",
        "choice3": "5,399",
        "choice4": "5,499"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 4,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 13",
      "details": "What is the smallest whole number that is 20,000 when rounded to the nearest ten thousand",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "19,000",
        "choice2": "17,000",
        "choice3": "14,000",
        "choice4": "12,000"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 14",
      "details": "What is the greatest whole number that is 20,000 when rounded to the nearest ten thousand",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "24,999",
        "choice2": "25,999",
        "choice3": "27,999",
        "choice4": "29,999"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 15",
      "details": "What is the smallest whole number that is 1,000,000 when rounded to the nearest million",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "1,000,001",
        "choice2": "999,000",
        "choice3": "666,000",
        "choice4": "500,000"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 4,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 16",
      "details": "What is the greatest whole number that is 1,000,000 when rounded to the nearest million",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "1,699,999",
        "choice2": "1,499,999",
        "choice3": "1,199,999",
        "choice4": "1,000,001"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 17",
      "details": "Estimate the sum of 1,889 and 2,989",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "2,000 + 2,000 = 4,000",
        "choice2": "2,000 + 3,000 = 5,000",
        "choice3": "1,000 + 2,000 = 3,000",
        "choice4": "1,000 + 3,000 = 4,000"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 18",
      "details": "Estimate the difference of 24,101 and 12,999",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "25,000 - 12,000 = 13,000",
        "choice2": "24,000 - 12,000 = 12,000",
        "choice3": "24,000 - 13,000 = 11,000",
        "choice4": "24,000 - 11,000 = 13,000"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 19",
      "details": "Estimate the product of 315 and 41",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "300 x 50 = 15,000",
        "choice2": "320 x 50 = 16,000 3",
        "choice3": "20 x 40 = 12,800",
        "choice4": "315 x 40 = 12,600"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 3,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Question 20",
      "details": "Estimate the result of 481 divided by 24",
      "choices": {
        "choice1": "480รท20 = 24",
        "choice2": "400รท20 = 20",
        "choice3": "500รท25 = 20",
        "choice4": "480รท24 = 20"
      },
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "topic": "Estimation"
    }
  ]
}